

DAVID CANO ZAFRA

PHYSICS ENGINEER, DATA SCIENTIST AND ENGINEER

ADRESS C/ MARIA DE GUZMAN, MADRID

NUMBER 629985034

E-MAIL
DAVID.CANO221@GMAIL.COM

WEBPAGE: https://davidcano221.github.io/davidcano/

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Physics engineer specializing in Data Science and Engineering. 1-year experience analyzing digital biomedical signals, and a Master in Biomedical Engineering/Data Processing. I consider myself a curious person willing and able to learn fast and constantly improve. I can adapt to different scenarios providing perspectives from the mathematical, physics, and engineering fields.

EDUCATION

MSC DATA SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING CURRENTLY

WEBPAGES CREATION, PROGRAMMING, AND DESIGN 2020

E-LEARNING TRAINING 2020

MSC BIOMEDICAL ENGINEERING 2018 - 2020

BSC PYSHICS ENGINEERING 2014 - 2018

LANGUAGES

SPANISH
CATALAN
ENGLISH
GERMAN

EXPERIENCE

RESEARCHER - UPC SEPT. 2018 - JAN. 2020

- Acquisition, filtering and visualization of digital biomedical signals.
- · Utilization of Matlab and Python.

STUDENT SUPPORT - UPC

MAR. 2018

 To inform college students who are interested in the degree about the features of it.

CUSTOMER SUPPORT - DECATHLON JUNE 2017 - SEPT. 2017

- To attend and support the customer.
- To help the teammates of other departments.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS



PYTHON



R



MATLAB



TABLEAU



EXCEL

SOL

SOL

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

VERSATILITY RESPONSIBILITY

WILLINGNESS PROBLEM
TO LEARN SOLVING

ASSERTIVENESS TEAMWORK